Guide to the Time Inc. Annex Files 1854, 1909, 1923-2014 MS 3009-RG 39
New-York Historical Society
- History: The March of Time: Movie: 1935-1941, 1935-1944, 1964-1968 (Offsite-box 3871, Folder 3-4)
- History: The March of Time: Movie: 1942-1951, 1942-1947, 1970 (Offsite-box 3871, Folder 5-6)
- History: The March of Time: Radio, 1930-1941, 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 3871, Folder 7-8)
- History: Newsbureau: 1940 and Before, 1935, 1966, undated (Offsite-box 3871, Folder 9)
- History: Newsbureaus: 1943 and Later, 1943-1949, 1957-1960 (Offsite-box 3871, Folder 10)
- History: Prologue and Epilogue, 1948-1951, 1967-1971 (Offsite-box 3871, Folder 11)
- History: Sports Illustrated: 1953 and Before, 1950-1957, 1964, 1972 (Offsite-box 3871, Folder 12-14)
- History: Sports Illustrated: 1954: January-August, 1936, 1953-1964, undated (Offsite-box 3871, Folder 15-16)
- History: Sports Illustrated: 1954: August-December, 1953-1970 (Offsite-box 3871, Folder 17)
- History: Sports Illustrated: 1955-1959, 1955-1958, undated (Offsite-box 3871, Folder 18-19)
- History: Sports Illustrated: 1960-1964, 1955-1958, 1966, undated (Offsite-box 3871, Folder 20-21)
- History: Tide, 1927, 1965, undated (Offsite-box 3871, Folder 22)
- History: 1936 and Before: Business, 1929-1936, 1966-1967, undated (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 1)
- History: 1936 and Before: Fortune, 1930-1935, 1956, 1965-1966, undated (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 2-3)
- History: 1936 and Before: Life Folder #1, 1929-1936, 1956-1958, 1965 (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 4)
- History: 1936 and Before: Life Folder #2, 1936-1937, 1956, 1966 (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 5-6)
- History: 1936 and Before: Time, 1924-1936, 1955, 1959-1967 (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 7-9)
- History: 1937: Business, 1937-1938 (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 10)
- History: 1937: Fortune, 1937, undated (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 11)
- History: 1937: Life: Business, 1937-1938, 1956, 1967 (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 12-13)
- History: 1937: Life: Edit, 1936-1938 (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 14)
- History: 1937: Time, 1937, undated (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 15)
- History: 1938: Business, 1937-1948, 1966, undated (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 16)
- History: 1938: Business [RESTRICTED], 1938, undated (Offsite-box R69)
- History: 1938: Edit, 1939, undated (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 17)
- History: 1938: Fortune (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 18)
- History: 1938: Life: Business (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 19)
- History: 1938: Life: Edit (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 20)
- History: 1938: Time: Business (Offsite-box 3872, Folder 21)
- History: 1939 Time: Edit, 1938, 1944, 1954 (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 1)
- History: 1939: Business, 1939, 1967 (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 2)
- History: 1939: Business [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R69)
- History: 1939: Edit: January-April, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 3)
- History: 1939: Edit: May-August, 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 4)
- History: 1939: Edit: September-December, 1939, 1962-1967 (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 5-6)
- History: 1939: Fortune, 1937, 1944, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 7)
- History: 1939: Time, 1939, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 8)
- History: 1940: Business, 1940, 1967 (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 9)
- History: 1940: Edit: January-June, 1940, 1957, 1966 (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 10-11)
- History: 1940: Edit: July (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 12)
- History: 1940: Edit: August (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 13)
- History: 1940: Edit: September (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 14)
- History: 1940: Edit: October (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 15)
- History: 1940: Edit: November (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 16)
- History: 1940: Edit: December (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 17)
- History: 1940: Fortune (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 18)
- History: 1940: Journalism Campaign, 1939-1941 (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 19)
- History: 1941: Business, 1940-1941, 1967 (Offsite-box 3873, Folder 20)
- History: 1941: Business [RESTRICTED], 1940-1941, 1967 (Offsite-box R69)
- History: 1941 Edit: January-March, 1941-1942, 1948, 1967 (Offsite-box 3874, Folder 1)
- History: 1941 Edit: April-June (Offsite-box 3874, Folder 2)
- History: 1941 Edit: July (Offsite-box 3874, Folder 3)
- History: 1941 Edit: August-September (Offsite-box 3874, Folder 4)
- History: 1941 Edit: October (Offsite-box 3874, Folder 5)
- History: 1941 Edit: November-December, 1941-1946 (Offsite-box 3874, Folder 6)
- History: 1941-1942: Edit: December-June, 1941-1942, 1966 (Offsite-box 3874, Folder 7-8)
- History: 1942: Business, 1968 (Offsite-box 3874, Folder 9)
- History: 1942: Edit: July-December (Offsite-box 3874, Folder 10-11)
- History: 1942: Edit: Supplementary Documents (empty), undated (Offsite-box 3874, Folder 12)
- History: 1943: Business, 1943, 1968, 1969 (Offsite-box 3874, Folder 13)
- History: 1943: Edit: January-June, 1943-1944, 1967 (Offsite-box 3874, Folder 14-15)
- History: 1943: Edit: July-December (Offsite-box 3874, Folder 16-17)
- History: 1944: Business, 1944-1946 (Offsite-box 3875, Folder 1)
- History: 1944: Edit: January-June (Offsite-box 3875, Folder 2-3)
- History: 1944: Edit: July-December, 1944-1945 (Offsite-box 3875, Folder 4-5)
- History: 1945: Business, 1944-1946, 1969 (Offsite-box 3875, Folder 6-7)
- History: 1945: Edit: January-June (Offsite-box 3875, Folder 8)
- History: 1945: Edit: July-December, 1945, 1951, 1953 (Offsite-box 3875, Folder 9-10)
- History: 1946: Business, 1946-1947, 1969 (Offsite-box 3875, Folder 11)
- History: 1946: Edit, 1946-1951, 1957, 1969 (Offsite-box 3875, Folder 12-13)
- History: 1947: Business, 1947-1948, 1969 (Offsite-box 3875, Folder 14)
- History: 1947: Edit, 1946-1949, 1969 (Offsite-box 3875, Folder 15-16)
- History: 1948: Business, 1949-1949, 1963, 1969 (Offsite-box 3875, Folder 17)
- History: 1948: Edit: January-June, 1948-1952, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 3876, Folder 1-2)
- History: 1948, 1948-1952, 1961, 1968 (Offsite-box 3876, Folder 3)
- History: 1949: Business, 1949, 1969 (Offsite-box 3876, Folder 4)
- History: 1949: Edit, 1949, 1969 (Offsite-box 3876, Folder 5)
- History: 1950: Business, 1950, 1969 (Offsite-box 3876, Folder 6)
- History: 1950: Edit, 1950-1952, undated (Offsite-box 3876, Folder 7)
- History: 1951: Business (Offsite-box 3876, Folder 8)
- History: 1951: Edit (Offsite-box 3876, Folder 9-10)
- History: 1951-52: Edit (Joe McCarthy and Time Cover), 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 3876, Folder 11)
- History: 1952: Business, 1957-1964, 1970 (Offsite-box 3876, Folder 12-13)
- History: 1952: Edit (Offsite-box 3876, Folder 14)
- History: 1972: Edit (Presidential Election) (Offsite-box 3876, Folder 15)
- History: 1972: Edit (Presidential Election) (Offsite-box 3877, Folder 1)
- History: 1953: Business (Offsite-box 3877, Folder 2)
- History: 1953: Edit Part One, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 3877, Folder 3-4)
- History: 1953: Edit Part Two, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 3877, Folder 5-6)
- History: 1954: Business, 1954, 1970 (Offsite-box 3877, Folder 7)
- History: 1954: Edit Part One (Offsite-box 3877, Folder 8-9)
- History: 1954: Edit Part Two, 1953-1954, 1969 (Offsite-box 3877, Folder 10-11)
- History: 1955: Business, 1953-1956, 1970 (Offsite-box 3877, Folder 12)
- History: 1955: Edit Part One, 1955, undated (Offsite-box 3877, Folder 13-14)
- History: 1955: Edit Part Two, 1954-1956, undated (Offsite-box 3877, Folder 16-16)
- History: 1956: Business, 1953-1957, 1970 (Offsite-box 3878, Folder 1-2)
- History: 1956: Edit, 1956-1959, undated (Offsite-box 3878, Folder 3)
- History: 1957: Business, 1955-1957, 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 3878, Folder 4-5)
- History: 1957: Edit, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 3878, Folder 6)
- History: 1958: Business, 1957-1958, 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 3878, Folder 7-8)
- History: 1958: Edit, 1958, undated (Offsite-box 3878, Folder 9)
- History: 1958-1961: Life: Edit, 1958-1961, 1970 (Offsite-box 3878, Folder 10)
- History: 1959: Business, 1958-1961, 1970 (Offsite-box 3878, Folder 11-12)
- History: 1959: Edit, 1958-1959 (Offsite-box 3879, Folder 1-2)
- History: 1960: Business, 1960-1970 (Offsite-box 3879, Folder 3)
- History: 1960: Edit, 1956-1960, 1967 (Offsite-box 3879, Folder 4-5)
- History: Sports Illustrated: 1954: August-December [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R69)
- Home Box Office: Affiliate, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 3879, Folder 6)
- Home Box Office: Anniversaries: 10th Anniversary 1984, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 3879, Folder 7)
- Home Box Office: Anniversary (10th), 1982 (Offsite-box 4015, Folder 5)
- Home Box Office: Cablevision Program Guides, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3879, Folder 8)
- Home Box Office: Cinemax Guides, 1980-1992, 2002-2004 (Offsite-box 3879, Folder 9-13)
- Home Box Office: Cinemax Guides, 1980-1992, 2002-2004 (Offsite-box 3880, Folder 1-3)
- Home Box Office: "Festival" Guides 1986-, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 3880, Folder 4)
- Home Box Office: Hobnobber: 1980-1985 (Offsite-box 3880, Folder 5-6)
- Home Box Office: Hobnobber: 1986-, 1986-1997 (Offsite-box 3880, Folder 7-10)
- Home Box Office: Hobnobber: June-September 1996, February-April 1997, June-August 1997, 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 3880, Folder 11)
- Home Box Office: Hotel/Motel Guides, 1978-1980, 1986 (Offsite-box 3880, Folder 12)
- Home Box Office: Open Line Employee Newsletter, 1984-1992 (Offsite-box 3880, Folder 13)
- Home Box Office: Program Guide Dummy, undated (Offsite-box 3880, Folder 14)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides: 1972 (Offsite-box 3880, Folder 15)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides: 1973 (Offsite-box 3880, Folder 16)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides: 1974 (Offsite-box 3880, Folder 17)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3880, Folder 18)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides 1975 and 1976, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3880, Folder 19)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides 1975 and 1976, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3881, Folder 1-2)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides 1977 and 1978, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3881, Folder 3-5)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides 1979 and 1980, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 3881, Folder 6-8)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 3881, Folder 9-10)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides 1983 (Offsite-box 3881, Folder 11)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides 1985-1989 (Offsite-box 3881, Folder 12-13)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides 1991-1994 (Offsite-box 3882, Folder 1-3)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides 1995-1999 (Offsite-box 3882, Folder 4-5)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides 2000-, 2000-2005 (Offsite-box 3882, Folder 6)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3882, Folder 7)
- Home Box Office (HBO) Program Guides, 1973-1979 (Offsite-box 4043, Folder 1)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3882, Folder 8)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3882, Folder 9)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides, 1979 (Offsite-box 3882, Folder 10)
- Home Box Office: Program Guides Gerald M. Levin (GML), 1974-1977, undated (Offsite-box 3882, Folder 11-12)
- Home Box Office (HBO): Promotion, 1978, 1987 (Offsite-box 4044, Folder 1)
- Home Box Office: Surveys and Studies: 1974: "The Second Year", A Report to the Motion Picture Industry, undated (Offsite-box 3882, Folder 13)
- Home Box Office: Surveys and Studies: 1979: Attitudes Towards Cable Television (Offsite-box 3882, Folder 14)
- Home Box Office: Take One, 1977 (Offsite-box 3882, Folder 15)
- Home Box Office: Take One and Take Two, 1977-1979 (Offsite-box 3882, Folder 16)
- Home Box Office: Take Two Guides, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 3882, Folder 17-18)
- Home Box Office: 1972 and Before: Hofstra Lease Television Microwave Receiver and Transmitter, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 3882, Folder 19)
- Home Box Office: 1972 and Before: Hofstra Lease TV Microwave Receiver+ [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Offsite-box R69)
- Home Box Office: 1972 and Before: Microwave Path Survey New York City to Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 3883, Folder 1-2)
- Home Box Office: 1972 and Before: Programming: Madison Square Garden [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R69)
- Home Box Office: 1972 and Before: Regulatory (I) (Offsite-box 3883, Folder 3-4)
- Home Box Office: 1972 and Before: Regulatory (II) (Offsite-box 3883, Folder 5-6)
- Home Box Office: 1972: Regulatory [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R69)
- Home Box Office: 1973: Regulatory (Offsite-box 3883, Folder 7-8)
- Home Box Office: 1974: Regulatory (Offsite-box 3883, Folder 9-10)
- Home Box Office: 1975: Regulatory (Offsite-box 3883, Folder 11)
- Home Box Office: 1976: Regulatory (Offsite-box 3883, Folder 12)
- Home Box Office: 1983: Regulatory (Offsite-box 3883, Folder 13)
- Home Box Office: 1984: Regulatory (Offsite-box 3883, Folder 14)
- Home Box Office: Miscellaneous, undated (Offsite-box 3883, Folder 15)
- Home Box Office: Miscellaneous, undated (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 1)
- Huntington Cable Television (CATV) Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1965-1972 (Offsite-box R69)
- House and Home, 1960, 1962 (Offsite-box 4015, Folder 6)
- Information Systems Monthly Newsletter and Descriptive Material, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 2-3)
- Inland Container Corporation: 1977 (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 4)
- Instyle: Imitations, 1996-1998 (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 5)
- Instyle: Issue June 2004 (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 6)
- Instyle: Surveys and Studies: 1998 Marketing Plan Competitive Category Overview (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 7)
- International: Afghanistan: Reports, undated (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 8)
- International: Africa Newsbureau, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 9)
- International: Africa, General: Reports, 1952-1959, 1965 (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 10)
- International: Africa General: Miscellaneous, 1943, 1959-1970, undated (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 11)
- International: Alaska (Before Statehood), 1941-1949 (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 12)
- International: Albania, 1946, 1964 (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 13)
- International: Algeria: Reports, 1963 (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 14)
- International: Algeria: Miscellaneous, 1944, 1966, 1978 (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 15)
- International: Angola: Reports, 1956-1964 (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 16)
- International: Argentina: Reports, 1948-1965 (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 17)
- International: Argentina: Miscellaneous, 1937-1953, 1981, undated (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 18-19)
- International: Australia: Offices, 1959-1969 (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 20)
- International: Australia: Reports 1946-1959 (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 21-22)
- International: Australia: Reports 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 3884, Folder 23)
- International: Australia: Reports 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 1)
- International: Australia: Reports 1962-1966, 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 2-3)
- International: Australia: Miscellaneous 1955 and Before, 1940-1955 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 4-5)
- International: Australia: Miscellaneous 1956 and Later, 1956-1967, 1969-1976, undated (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 6-7)
- International: Australia: Miscellaneous: 1956 and later [RESTRICTED], 1960 (Offsite-box R69)
- International: Austria: Reports, 1947-1965 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 8)
- International: Austria: Miscellaneous, 1938, 1946-1948, 1960-1964 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 9)
- International: Bahamas: Reports, 1952-1966 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 10)
- International: Bahrain: Reports, 1957-1965 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 11)
- International: Bahrain: Miscellaneous, 1961 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 12)
- International: Barbados: Reports, 1952, 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 13)
- International: Barbados: Miscellaneous, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 14)
- International: Belgium: Reports, 1948-1965 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 15)
- International: Belgium: Miscellaneous, 1945, 1958-1965 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 16)
- International: Bermuda: Reports, 1961 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 17)
- International: Bermuda: Miscellaneous, 1941-1943, 1963-1966 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 18)
- International: Bolivia: Reports, 1951-1958 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 19)
- International: Brazil: Reports 1943-1955 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 20-21)
- International: Brazil: Reports 1943-1955, 1948 (Offsite-box 4044, Folder 2)
- International: Brazil: Report 1956-1966 (Offsite-box 3885, Folder 20-23)
- International: Brazil: Miscellaneous, 1933-1970, undated (Offsite-box 3886, Folder 1)
- International: Brazil: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1944 (Offsite-box R69)
- International: Brazil: Time-Life News Service, 1943-1961 (Offsite-box 3886, Folder 2)
- International: Britain: The March of Time: Movie: Publicity, 1935-1946 (Offsite-box 3886, Folder 3)
- International: Britain: The March of Time: Movie: Miscellaneous, 1935-1939, 1945-1949, undated (Offsite-box 3886, Folder 4-5)
- International: Britain: Newsbureau, 1935-1939, 1945-1949, undated (Offsite-box 3886, Folder 6)
- International: Britain: Offices: New Building: 1953: Promotion and Publicity, 1951-1953, undated (Offsite-box 3886, Folder 7-8)
- International: Britain: Offices: New Building: 1953: Miscellaneous, 1935-1961 (Offsite-box 3886, Folder 9)
- International: Britain: Offices: Miscellaneous, 1943, 1949-1957 (Offsite-box 3886, Folder 10)
- International: Britain: Reports, 1945-1957 (Offsite-box 3886, Folder 11-12)
- International: Britain: Reports 1945-1955, 1947 (Offsite-box 4044, Folder 3)
- International: Britain: Reports 1956-1966, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 3886, Folder 13)
- International: Britain: Miscellaneous 1946 and Before, 1931-1946 (Offsite-box 3886, Folder 14-15)
- International: Britain: Miscellaneous 1946 and before [RESTRICTED], 1936 (Offsite-box R69)
- International: Britain: 1947-1959 [RESTRICTED], 1953 (Offsite-box R69)
- International: Britain: Miscellaneous 1947-1959 (Offsite-box 3886, Folder 16-17)
- International: Britain: Miscellaneous 1960 and Later, 1960-1968 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 1-2)
- International: British Honduras, 1941-1952, 1962-1964 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 3)
- International: Bulgaria: Reports, 1965 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 4)
- International: Bulgaria: Miscellaneous, 1946-1947, 1964-1967 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 5)
- International: Burma: Reports, 1950-1966 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 6)
- International: Burma: Reports [RESTRICTED], 1952 (Offsite-box R69)
- International: Burma: Miscellaneous, 1958-1966 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 7)
- International: Cambodia: Reports, 1958-1961 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 8)
- International: Cambodia: Miscellaneous, 1959-1964 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 9)
- International: Cameroon: Reports, 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 10)
- International: Canada: 1961 Royal Commission on Publications (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 11)
- International: Canada: 1975 Royal Commission on Publications (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 12)
- International: Canada: 1955 and Before, 1933-1955 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 13)
- International: Canada: 1956 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 14-15)
- International: Canada: 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 16)
- International: Canada: 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 17-18)
- International: Canada: 1961: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 19)
- International: Canada: 1961 Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R69)
- International: Canada: 1962 and Later, 1962-1971 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 20)
- International: Canada: 1962 and Later [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R69)
- International: Canada: The March of Time, 1936-1943 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 21)
- International: Canada: The March of Time [RESTRICTED], 1941 (Offsite-box R69)
- International: Canal Zone: Reports, 1951-1963 (Offsite-box 3887, Folder 22)
- International: Canal Zone: Miscellaneous, 1960-1964 (Offsite-box 3888, Folder 1)
- International: Canary Island: Reports, 1956, 1962-1965 (Offsite-box 3888, Folder 2)
- International: Canary Island: Miscellaneous, 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 3888, Folder 3)
- International: Chile: Reports, 1943-1963 (Offsite-box 3888, Folder 4)
- International: Chile: Miscellaneous, 1938-1941, 1950-1968 (Offsite-box 3888, Folder 5-6)
- International: Ceylon: Reports, 1941, 1947, 1953-1965, undated (Offsite-box 3888, Folder 7-8)
- International: Ceylon: Miscellaneous, 1960-1966 (Offsite-box 3888, Folder 9)
- International: China: Reports, 1946-1948 (Offsite-box 3888, Folder 10)
- International: China: Miscellaneous, 1932-1950, 1956-1965, 1972, 1979 (Offsite-box 3888, Folder 11-12)
- International: Colombia: Reports 1942-1953 (Offsite-box 3888, Folder 13-14)
- International: Colombia: Reports 1954-1961, 1954-1960 (Offsite-box 3888, Folder 15)
- International: Colombia: Time-Life News Service, 1948 (Offsite-box 3888, Folder 16)
- International: Colombia: Miscellaneous, 1935, 1942-1966 (Offsite-box 3888, Folder 17-18)
- International: Costa Rica: Reports, 1951-1965 (Offsite-box 3888, Folder 19)
- International: Costa Rica: Reports, 1951-1965 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 1)
- International: Costa Rica: Miscellaneous, 1946-1948, 1963-1966 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 2)
- International: Cuba: Reports, 1948-1959 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 3-4)
- International: Cuba: Miscellaneous: 1952 and Before, 1933, 1941-1952 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 5)
- International: Cuba: Miscellaneous: 1952 and Before [RESTRICTED], 1961 (Offsite-box R69)
- International: Cuba: Miscellaneous: 1953-1958 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 6)
- International: Cuba: 1953-1958 [RESTRICTED], 1954 (Offsite-box R69)
- International: Cuba: 1959 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 7)
- International: Cuba: 1959 [RESTRICTED], 1954-1959 (Offsite-box R69)
- International: Cuba: 1960 and Later, 1960-1966, 1977 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 8)
- International: Cuba: 1960 and Later [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R69)
- International: Cyprus: Reports, 1955-1964 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 9)
- International: Cyprus: Miscellaneous, 1946, 1962-1964 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 10)
- International: Czechoslovakia: Reports, 1946, 1962-1964 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 11)
- International: Czechoslovakia: Miscellaneous, 1946, 1962-1964 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 12)
- International: Dahomey: Reports, 1965 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 13)
- International: Denmark: Reports, 1945-1946, 1956-1965 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 14)
- International: Denmark: Miscellaneous, 1945-1946, 1962-1964, undated (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 15)
- International: Dominican: Republic Reports, 1945-1946, 1962-1964, undated (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 16)
- International: Dominican: Republic Miscellaneous, 1936, 1946-1955, 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 17)
- International: Dubai: Reports, 1962 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 18)
- International: Ecuador: Reports, 1947-1956, 1963 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 19)
- International: Ecuador: Miscellaneous, 1940, 1946-1949, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 20)
- International: Egypt: Reports, 1954-1965 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 21)
- International: Egypt: Miscellaneous, 1941-1956, 1958-1971 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 22)
- International: Egypt: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R69)
- International: El Salvador: Reports, 1957-1964 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 23)
- International: El Salvador: Miscellaneous, 1947, 1960-1966 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 24)
- International: Ethiopia: Reports, 1952-1966 (Offsite-box 3889, Folder 25)
- International: Ethiopia: Miscellaneous, 1946, 1960-1964 (Offsite-box 3890, Folder 1)
- International: Europe, 1946, 1960-1964 (Offsite-box 3890, Folder 2)
- International: Fiji, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 3890, Folder 3)
- International: Finland: Reports, 1946-1963 (Offsite-box 3890, Folder 4)
- International: Finland: Miscellaneous, 1937, 1944-1946, 1952, 1962-1964 (Offsite-box 3890, Folder 5)
- International: France: 1946 French Press Study, 1944-1946 (Offsite-box 3890, Folder 6)
- International: France: The March of Time: Movie and Radio, 1935-1937, 1948, undated (Offsite-box 3890, Folder 7)
- International: France: Newsbureau, 1944-1946, 1953-1956, 1963 (Offsite-box 3890, Folder 8)
- International: France: Offices, 1930-1940, 1948-1969, undated (Offsite-box 3890, Folder 9)
- International: France: Offices, 1946 (Offsite-box 3264, Folder 13)
- International: France: Offices [RESTRICTED], 1955-1963, undated (Offsite-box R69)
- International: France: Reports, 1935-1960, undated (Offsite-box 3890, Folder 10)
- International: France: Miscellaneous 1945 and Before, 1932-1949 (Offsite-box 3890, Folder 11)